ollando.com 2019-04-13

# Privacy Policy | Ollando

**Introduction**

Personal information about customers and website visitors is held securely and is treated with the utmost care. Crosmo ltd is committed to protecting the privacy of its customers and visitors to its websites as being an absolute necessity to the operation of its business.

Crosmo ltd complies with the requirements of the Personal Data Protection Act and other privacy legislation for accurate processing of personal data. The party responsible for data processing (Controller) is Crosmo ltd (Zekeringstraat 17, 1014 BM Amsterdam, The Netherlands). The Dutch Data Protection Authority in The Hague is notified of all processing of personal data.

**Processing personal data**

Data is stored and maintained in the course of providing our services. Your personal details are stored when you take out a subscription to a (mobile) service or a newsletter, when you are a participant to a promotion or invited to join a game. Data is also processed in the course of providing our services by other companies in the group, sponsors and partners, when making available the prize to the winner, register an interest in one of our services, or contact us for some other reason. The personal information we hold includes information such as contact details, mobile phone number, sub- and unsubscribe data, for instance to a (mobile) service or a newsletter, ordered products/services, information about payments, log files in the course of providing mobile services and/or where you have registered an interest in our different sorts of services.

We use this information for the fulfillment and processing of agreements with you (and our aggregators), to provide other services (by our subsidiaries and sponsors or partners), internal business processes and, to update customers of (new) products and services provided by us, other companies in the group or by sponsors and partners. Your (contact) details may also be passed on to sponsors and partners in order to provide you with information about offers or other relevant information. If you do not wish to receive this information, you can unsubscribe at any time.

**Use of subscribtion data**

In order to use our mobile services you are asked to complete a (usually country specific) subscription process. You are asked to specify a number of data, such as your name, address, postal code, residence, gender, mobile phone number, e-mail address and bank account number. These subscription data are used to send you information in the course of providing our (requested) services and to be able to bill these to you. We also want to keep you up-to-date with new, different sorts of products and services and interesting offers.

**Your mobile telephone number**

If you have specified your (mobile) telephone number this is used to confirm the kind of service and to conclude and perform the agreement with you. When you have indicated to be interested, we also use you (mobile) telephone number to communicate with you and to keep you informed of (new) products and services. You can unsubscribe at any moment by clicking on the link in the message which you receive on your mobile telephone.

**Your e-mail address**

When you have specified your e-mail address and have actively indicated to, for instance, receive a news letter or other information, then we can inform you (better) as a customer of different sorts of offers and prize actions. When you do not wish to receive this information, you can unsubscribe at any time by clicking on the link in the e-mail you received. You may also have given your consent to disclose your e-mail address to be sent offers and campaigns from other companies from time to time. Such companies are carefully selected beforehand. You can indicate and view this on the site most of the times.

**Reviewing for correction  **

You may review the data we maintain on you at any time. If such information is incorrect you can help us to correct these. To view or correct your data, you can send your request to the above mentioned address.  Please contact us also at the above address if you have questions or any queries about how we handle personal information.

**Preferences kind of products and services**

Our aim is to take into account your preferences as much as possible. If you are not interested in information about (new) relevant products and services, then we ask you to let us know on the special unsubscribe page on the site. Note: our service is aimed at sharing information with you on preferences for different kinds of products and services. If you opt to have all your data removed from our services, you may no longer receive information on offers and campaigns you may be interested in.

**Database records**

For the provision of our service we keep database records in order to have a robust control in place on our services (and our service providers). The purpose of this is to optimize the reliability of the service. The information derived from these data is used to prevent misuse of data and if necessary to comply with more detailed information queries from third parties on the basis of (self)regulation.

**Browsing session and IP-address**

We also make use of the IP-address of your computer. This IP-address is a number which automatically assigned to your computer when you have a browsing session on the internet, such as when you visit one of our sites or landing pages. They can be used to see which use has been made of the website and for drafting analyses and reports with non-identifiable information.

**Security  **

Due to the nature of the service and the trust which one must have in our service we have designed and implemented technical and organizational measures governing an adequate level of security and ensure compliance with these measures.

**Cookies**

Sites which transmit advertisements are making use of cookies to keep count of which advertisements have been shown. These cookies are placed by the company which provides these advertisements. The only purpose of these cookies is to transmit the communication necessary to show the advertisement on the website or to provide the requested service after clicking the advertisement on the website. These ‘clicks’ give us information which is in the interests of statistical analysis on a non-identifiable level. Your personal use cannot be derived from such use.

**Links**

On this site you see a number of hyperlinks to other websites. We cannot be held responsible for the data processing activities by these organizations. Read the privacy policy, if present, of the site you are visiting.

**Adjustments**

We reserve the right to make adjustments to this privacy policy. Important adjustments are made know on this site in the privacy policy.

Amsterdam , 26 March 2013
